sunsigns.org 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy

## **Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy for **https://www.sunsigns.org**

The privacy of our visitors to  **https://www.sunsigns.org** is crucial to us.

At **SunSigns.org** , we recognize that privacy of your personal information is essential. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **[https://www.sunsigns.org](https://www.sunsigns.org/)** and use our mobile products, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. This Privacy Policy covers SunSigns.Org’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) and other data that SunSigns.Org gathers when you are accessing SunSigns.Org’s Service.

## What Personal Information Does SunSigns.Org Collect?

###  **Log Files**

As with most other websites and mobile platforms, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. We treat this data as non-Personal Information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. SunSigns.Org only uses this data in aggregate form. We may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site and / or mobile applications, so that our partners may also understand how often people use their services and our Service.

###  **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

####  **Personal Information You Provide to Us:**

  * We collect (via partner’s SDKs) information, some of which may be considered as personal information. Such as but not limited to OS version, phone resolution, advertising id, number of ads displayed in the past, etc.
  * We do **not** store any personal information on SunSigns.Org servers.
  * We do **not** sell or rent information collected independently by SunSigns.Org. We do not share any user information collected independently by SunSigns.Org with our advertising partners. **Any information collected by our partners is** strictly **via their SDKs.**

###  **Analytics**

SunSigns.Org utilizes analytics partners to collect, store and analyze analytical data. This data may include ID identifying unique installation on a device which will change if our apps are reinstalled or “Advertising ID” where applicable to uniquely identify each device to be able to track session length and other metrics for each device.

### Partners

####  **Advertising Partners***

We work with the following partners who may serve ads and collect necessary information to do so via their respective SDKs:

  *  **AdMob – https://admob.com**

* Please note that this list may periodically change as we change advertising partners

####  **Analytics Partners***

  * Firebase – http://firebase.google.com

* Please note that this list may periodically change as we change advertising partners

We also use third party advertisements on **https://www.sunsigns.org** to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)

 **DoubleClick DART cookies** We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your device when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest-based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non-personally identifiable information.” It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](https://www.sunsigns.org/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you can interact with our site and app as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

SunSigns.Org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SunSigns.Org’s behalf or to provide services available at SunSigns.Org’s website and mobile platforms, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SunSigns.Org services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

SunSigns.Org will never rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. SunSigns.Org discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when SunSigns.Org believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SunSigns.Org, third parties or the public at large.

In addition, if SunSigns.Org sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, SunSigns.Org may transfer your personally identifying information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

If you are a registered user of one of SunSigns.Org services, SunSigns.Org may occasionally give notification to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or keep you up to date with what’s going on with SunSigns.Org and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SunSigns.Org takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Security:

SunSigns.Org **does not** store any personally identifiable information. SunSigns.Org transfers potentially personally identifiable information to its advertising and analytics partners via the respective SDKs.

When we do so, SunSigns.Org and its partners use commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard potentially personal identifying information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SunSigns.Org may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SunSigns.Org’s sole discretion. SunSigns.Org encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our services, including but not limited to our website, mobile applications and our web services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Questions or Concerns?

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or SunSigns.Org’s collection and use of data, please contact SunSigns.Org. [Click here to contact us](https://www.sunsigns.org/contact-us/)

NAI opt-out link: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/)
